So building community happens in a number of ways, but one of the ways that I want to build community is I'm implementing something on my Instagram page, and it is also on my YouTube page, Amanda Seals TV.
From this point forward, it's not about just y'all being rude to me, it's about y'all being rude to each other.
And if I see folks being rude to folks on my pages, you will be removed and blocked.
There's no version of us as community being able to talk to each other if we can't disagree with each other without shading each other.
And without talking to each other, we can't identify solutions, we can't identify problems, we can't move in unison.
You hear me?
All this calling people out of their names, done.
All this adding in little snide things like, damn, can't you even?
Done.
All the little act-outs that y'all, and let me say we, that we do on this internet where we get to act out our little sass with folks because we don't have to deal with the repercussions of them being in our face, all of that is done in my spaces.
If I see you do it, I'm going to remove you because that's not the energy I want, and that's not the energy that I want to continue to perpetuate.
So I'm holding myself to that standard, and I'm holding y'all to that standard.
Ba-dum-dum!